- [Exercise Instructor] Keep
breathin', nice and even,
last one!
Two, three, four.
- [Reporter] In the news.
♪ Hi, my name is, what ♪
♪ My name is, who ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, huh ♪
♪ My name is, what ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, what ♪
♪ Excuse me ♪
♪ My name is, who ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Can I have the attention
of the class for one second ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, kids, do you like Primus ♪
♪ Wanna see me stick nine inch nails ♪
♪ Through each one of my eyelids ♪
♪ Wanna copy me and do
exactly like I did ♪
♪ Try (beep) and get messed
up worse than my life is ♪
♪ My brain's dead weight, I'm
tryin' to get my head straight ♪
♪ But I can't figure
out which Spice Girl ♪
♪ I wanna impregnate ♪
♪ And Dr. Dre said, Slim
Shady, you a basehead, uh-huh ♪
♪ Then why's your face
red, man, you wasted ♪
♪ Well, since age 12, I
felt like a caged elf ♪
♪ Who stayed to himself in
one space chasin' his tail ♪
♪ Got ticked off and ripped
Pamela Lee's lips off ♪
♪ And kissed 'em and said ♪
♪ I ain't know silicone was
supposed to be this soft ♪
♪ I'm 'bout to pass out and
crash and fall in the grass ♪
♪ Faster than a fat man
who sat down too fast ♪
♪ Come here, lady ♪
♪ Shady, wait a minute,
that's my girl, dawg ♪
♪ I don't give a damn, Dre
sent me to tick the world off ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, what ♪
♪ My name is, who ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, huh ♪
♪ My name is, what ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, what ♪
♪ My name is, who ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, huh ♪
♪ My name is, what ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ My English teacher wanted
to flunk me in junior high ♪
♪ Thanks a lot, next semester I'll be 35 ♪
♪ I smacked him in his
face with an eraser ♪
♪ Chased him with a stapler ♪
♪ And told him to change
the grade on the paper ♪
♪ Walked in the strip club,
had my jacket zipped up ♪
♪ Served the bartender, then
walked out with the tip cup ♪
♪ Extraterrestrial running over
pedestrians in a spaceship ♪
♪ While they're screaming at
me, "Let's just be friends" ♪
♪ 99 percent of my life, I was lied to ♪
♪ I just found out my mom
does more (beep) than I do ♪
♪ I told her I'd grow up
to be a famous rapper ♪
♪ Make a record about doin'
(beep) and name it after her ♪
♪ Here mom ♪
♪ You know you blew up when
the women rush your stands ♪
♪ And try to touch your hands
like some screamin' Usher fans ♪
♪ This guy at White Castle
asked for my autograph ♪
♪ Dude, can I get your autograph ♪
♪ So I signed it, Dear Dave,
thanks for the support, (beep) ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, huh ♪
♪ My name is, who ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, what ♪
♪ My name is, who ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, huh ♪
♪ My name is, who ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, what ♪
♪ My name is, who ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Stop the tape, this kid
needs to be locked away ♪
♪ Dr. Dre, don't just
stand there, operate ♪
♪ I'm not ready to leave,
it's too scary to die ♪
♪ I'll have to be carried
inside the cemetery ♪
♪ And buried alive ♪
♪ Am I comin' or goin' ♪
♪ I can barely decide ♪
♪ I just drank a fifth of
Kool-Aid, (beep) go ahead ♪
♪ All my life I was very deprived ♪
♪ I ain't had a woman in years ♪
♪ And my palms are too hairy to hide ♪
♪ Clothes ripped like
the Incredible Hulk ♪
♪ I spit when I talk, I'll
(beep) anything that walks ♪
♪ When I was little, I
used to get so hungry ♪
♪ I would throw fits ♪
♪ How you gonna breastfeed me,
Mom, you ain't got no (beep) ♪
♪ I lay awake and strap
myself in the bed ♪
♪ With a bulletproof vest on ♪
♪ And tap myself in the head ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm steamin' mad ♪
♪ And by the way, when you see my dad ♪
♪ Ask him if he bought a
porno mag and seen my ad ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, what ♪
♪ My name is, who ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, huh ♪
♪ My name is, what ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, who ♪
♪ My name is, huh ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪
♪ Hi, my name is, huh ♪
♪ My name is, who ♪
♪ My name is, chicka-chicka, Slim Shady ♪